pixorial.com 2012-12-15

# Pixorial - Privacy Policy

## Pixorial Privacy Policy

Effective June 1, 2010 

Pixorial, Inc. (“Pixorial”, “we”, or “us”) is dedicated to protecting your privacy online. This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) describes the ways we collect, store, use, and protect the personal information you share with us in connection with your use of the services we provide, including, without limitation, our website located at [www.pixorial.com](http://www.pixorial.com/) (the “Site”) and all of our services accessed through third party web sites (together referred to as the “Services”). By using our Services, you consent to the collection and use of information in the manner described below. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is part of our Terms of Use located at http://www.pixorial.com/pixorial/terms_of_use, and together these documents are the overall agreement between you and us. This Privacy Policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically. 

### Information We Collect Automatically

When you visit the Site, we automatically collect non-personal information including your IP address and standard web log information, such as your browser type and operating system, the date and time you access the Site, where you linked from, and the pages you visit. We use this information to help us make the Site more useful to visitors. For example, the information helps us determine the number of visitors to the Site and the types of technology our visitors use. We may use your IP address for additional purposes, including, without limitation, to diagnose or service technology problems reported by our users or engineers that are associated with the IP addresses controlled by a specific web company or internet service provider, to tailor advertising based on geographic area or other information derived from your IP address or to provide aggregate information derived from IP addresses to advertisers. 

While you are browsing, we do not collect any personal information about you, such as your name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address, unless you provide it to us voluntarily, for example, by sending us an e-mail message or requesting to be placed on our e-mail list. 

### Information We Collect From Registered Users 

When you open an account with us, we will ask you for your name and email address. If you are a registered user and you sign up for paid services, you may be asked to provide additional personal information, including, for example: 

  * Your phone number 
  * Your billing and mailing addresses 
  * Your credit card information 

We may obtain additional information about you from personal or third party websites, databases, publications, or other publicly available sources. It is your choice to post Content and make it publicly available. You are solely responsible for the Content you post. We also collect information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, and we store your Content, associated labels and editing meta-data. In addition, if you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence. If you give us permission in your privacy and application settings, located at <http://www.pixorial.com/account>, to share your Content with your friends, we may ask you for the names and e-mail addresses of such friends. You can choose not to provide any of the information we request, but then you may not be able to use all of our Services. For purposes of this Privacy Policy, “Content” includes, without limitation, data, text, information, screen names, graphics, photos, profiles, audio and video clips, and links to third-party content that you submit to us in connection with the Services. 

### Information We Do Not Collect

Pixorial does not knowingly collect or maintain any personal information from children under the age of 13. No part of the Site is intended or designed for the purpose of attracting any person under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, do not use the Site. If we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from a child under age 13, please contact us at [privacy[at]pixorial.com](https://web.archive.org/web/20121215131708id_/http%3A//www.pixorial.com/pixorial/\[email\]privacy\[at\]pixorial\[dot\]com?subject=Privacy%20Policy). 

### Information We Temporarily Place on Your Computer's Hard Drive 

A cookie is a small data file that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Pixorial uses temporary cookies in limited ways. When you log into your account, for example, we send a “session cookie” to your computer. This type of cookie helps us to recognize you if you visit multiple pages on the Site during the same session, so we do not need to keep asking you for your password. Once you log out or close your browser, the temporary cookies used by Pixorial expire, with the exception of a “remember me” cookie. Pixorial cookies do not generate personal data, do not read personal data from your computer, and are not linked to any information that could be used to identify you. 

You can always choose not to accept Pixorial's temporary cookies. Your browser instructions contain the information you need to modify your choices about cookies. By modifying your browser preferences, you can accept all cookies, be notified when a cookie is set, or reject all cookies. If you choose to reject all cookies, however, you may be unable to use all of our Services. 

### How We Protect Your Information

Pixorial takes commercially reasonable steps to protect the privacy and security of your personally identifiable information. 

  * Pixorial keeps the personal information you provide on servers that are located in physically secure facilities and protected by firewalls and other technological means. 
  * Your address and credit card number are encrypted once they are transmitted to us and stored in encrypted form. 
  * Our employees are trained to support these security measures and only have access to your information on a need-to-know basis. 

In addition, your customer account is password-protected. You can and should significantly increase the security of your personal information by changing your password three or four times a year and keeping it confidential. You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information at all times. While we strive to protect your information, we do not represent, warrant, or guarantee that your personal information will be protected against unauthorized access, loss, misuse, or alterations, and do not accept any liability for the security of the personal information submitted to us nor for your or third parties' use or misuse of personal information. 

### How We Use Your Information

Pixorial uses your personal information to conduct business with you. Some examples include: 

  * Creating and maintaining your account; 
  * Processing and fulfilling your orders;
  * Answering your e-mail messages;
  * Performing other administrative tasks; 
  * Communicating with you about Pixorial's Services; 
  * Sharing your Content with your friends and family at your direction;
  * Improving the quality and design of the Site, providing you with great service, and meeting your customer needs; and 
  * Operating and maintaining the Services.

### When We May Share Information  

Pixorial shares personal information with third parties under the following circumstances: 

  * We may share the information with companies who assist us with our business operations. Our contracts require that these service providers use your information only in connection with the business support functions they perform for us. They do not store, retain, access or otherwise use your personal information other than as necessary to provide you with our Services. Some examples of these business support functions include shipping and payment processing. 
  * We may share your information at your direction or with your consent. For example, when you request that we e-mail your Content to your friends and family. 
  * Subject to your privacy and application settings, located at <http://www.pixorial.com/account>, we may enable other Site users and third parties to view and edit your Content. These third-parties may include other websites, including social-networking providers such as Facebook, Linked-In, MySpace, etc., as well as individual subscribers to these third-party services. 
  * We may share the information with law enforcement, government officials, or other third parties when: 
    * We are compelled to do so by a subpoena, court order or other legal process; 
    * We need to do so to comply with the law; or 
    * We believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, or potential harm to the rights, property or safety of any person, to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims, to report suspected illegal activity, or to investigate violations of our Terms of Use. 
  * We may transfer or assign the information to another company or organization as part of a merger or acquisition, the sale or transfer of all or a portion of our business or assets or other change of control of our company. 

We do not sell or rent your personal information. However, we may sell or transfer non-individualized information to third parties, including summary or aggregated anonymous information about all or sub-groups of our users. 

### Keeping Your Information Accurate 

If you are a registered user, you can review and update your member profile, including your privacy and application settings, located at <http://www.pixorial.com/account>, using your user name and password. You may also send a message to the e-mail address noted in the “Contact Us” section below. We will make every reasonable effort to comply with your request. The accuracy of your profile information and settings is solely your responsibility. 

### Our E-mail Policy 

When you sign up for an account with us, you may receive periodic marketing communications from us, such as promotions, product and service updates and email newsletters. If you do not want to receive these communications, you may opt-out by configuring your ÒEmail preferencesÓ under account information, or by emailing us at [unsubscribe[at]pixorial.com](https://web.archive.org/web/20121215131708id_/http%3A//www.pixorial.com/pixorial/\[email\]unsubscribe\[at\]pixorial\[dot\]com?subject=Unsubscribe). We do not use the email or mailing addresses of your distribution contacts for marketing purposes. 

We do not use the email or mailing addresses of your distribution contacts for marketing purposes.  

### Links to Other Sites  

The Site may contain links to and the Services may be accessed through other websites that are beyond our control. The fact that we link to or provide services through another website is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party. We do not exercise control over third party websites and we are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices of other websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personally identifiable information from you. Other websites to which you link or through which you may use our Services may contain privacy policies that are different from this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to check the privacy policy of each website you visit before submitting any information to them. 

### International Visitors

The Site is hosted in the United States and governed by United States law. If you live outside of the United States and you give us personal data in conjunction with your use of the Site and the Services, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer and to the use of your information in accordance with United States law. 

### Amendments 

Pixorial reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time without notice by posting the revised version on this page and indicating at the top of this page the date the revised Privacy Policy will be effective. By continuing to use the Services after any changes, you are indicating your acceptance of such changes. It is your responsibility to regularly check the Site to determine if there have been changes to this Privacy Policy and to review such changes. 

### Contact Us 

If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or the way your personal information is being handled, please contact us by e-mail at [privacy[at]pixorial.com](https://web.archive.org/web/20121215131708id_/http%3A//www.pixorial.com/pixorial/\[email\]privacy\[at\]pixorial\[dot\]com) or by regular mail at: 

Pixorial, Inc.   
7670 S. Chester St, Unit 100    
Englewood, CO 80112-3479 

We will use reasonable efforts to promptly investigate and, if necessary, to correct any problem.
